I'm Shadi Abou-Zahra
Accessibility Strategy
and Technology Specialist
at W3C
The World Wide
Web Consortium
I'm Natalia Amelina
Senior National Project Officer
in Education
at the UNESCO Institute
for Information Technologies
in Education.
Join us in this course
to learn the fundamental skills
and key resources
that are becoming
increasingly important
across digital professions.
In according with statistics
people with disabilities
can make up around
15% of the population
and the United Nations Convention
on the Rights of Persons
with Disabilities
recognizes access to information
as a human right.
And you may know
that this Convention
was ratified
by 180 countries
all over the world
very likley including
your country too.
In this course
you will learn how people
with disabilities use the web
including different types
of assistive technologies
and adaptive strategies.
You will also learn
how web accessibility
improves user experience of
older people
people using mobile devices
and essentially for everyone.
And of course
you'll also learn all about
the international standards
from W3C
and training materials
and learn first steps
in creating accessible web content
This course was designed
for technical and
non-technical people.
If you work
with digital technologies
this course is ideal
for you to get started.